




  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Object-Oriented Programming :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/</link>
    <description>The best programming paradigm, “objectively” speaking!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:13:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/01-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/01-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this chapter was adapted from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author’s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.&#xA;A signature aspect of object-oriented languages is (as you might expect from the name), the existence of objects within the language. In this chapter, we take a deep look at objects, exploring why they were created, what they are at both a theoretical and practical level, and how they are used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encapsulation</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/02-encapsulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/02-encapsulation/</guid>
      <description>Video Materials&#xA;The first criteria that Alan Kay set for an object-oriented language was encapsulation. In computer science, the term encapsulation refers to organizing code into units, which provide two primary benefits:&#xA;Providing a mechanism for organizing complex software The ability to control access to encapsulated data and functionality Think back to the FORTRAN EPIC model we introduced in an earlier module. All of the variables in that program were declared globally, and there were thousands of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packages</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/03-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/03-packages/</guid>
      <description>Let’s start by focusing on encapsulation’s benefits to organizing our code by exploring some examples of encapsulation you may already be familiar with.&#xA;Packages The Java and Python libraries are organized into discrete units called packages. The primary purpose of this is to separate code units that potentially use the same name, which causes name collisions where the compiler or interpreter isn’t sure which of the possibilities you mean in your program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Type Systems</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/04-type-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/04-type-systems/</guid>
      <description>Video Materials&#xA;Before we go further into some object-oriented concepts, let’s briefly review one important concept in programming - data types and type systems.&#xA;Primitive Data Types Most programming languages include several primitive data types, which are the fundamental units of data that can be stored and represented by that programming language. Here’s a short list of those primitive data types for each language:&#xA;Data Java Python Whole Numbers int (byte, short, long) int Floating-point Numbers double (float) float Boolean Values boolean bool Single Character char str^[A string of length 1] String of Characters String^[This is not a primitive, but the String class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structs</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/05-structs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/05-structs/</guid>
      <description>Many object-oriented languages, such as C++ and C#, include the concept of a struct that form the basis of objects. A struct is an example of a compound data type, a data type composed from other types. This allows us to represent data in more complex ways by combining multiple primitive data types into a new type. This too, is a form of encapsulation, as it allows us to collect several values into a single data structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modules</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/06-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/06-modules/</guid>
      <description>It might seem like the kind of modules that Parnas was describing don’t exist in Java or Python, but they actually do - we just don’t call them “modules”. Consider how you would compute the square root of a number:&#xA;​ Java Python Math.sqrt(9.5); math.sqrt(9.5) The Math or math class in this example is actually used just like a module! We can’t see the underlying implementation of the sqrt() method, it just provides to us a well-defined interface (i.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State and Behavior</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/07-state-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/07-state-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Video Materials&#xA;The data stored in a program at any given moment (in the form of variables, objects, etc.) is the state of the program. Consider a variable:&#xA;int a = 5; The state of the variable a after this line is 5. If we then run:&#xA;a = a * 3; The state is now 15. Consider the Vector3 struct we defined earlier. If we create an instance of that struct in the variable b:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classes and Objects</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/08-classes-objects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/08-classes-objects/</guid>
      <description>The module-based encapsulation suggested by Parnas and his contemporaries grouped state and behavior together into smaller, self-contained units. Alan Kay and his co-developers took this concept a step farther. Alan Kay was heavily influenced by ideas from biology, and saw this encapsulation in similar terms to cells.&#xA;1&#xA;Biological cells are also encapsulated - the complex structures of the cell and the functions they perform are all within a cell wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access Modifiers</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/09-access-modifiers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/09-access-modifiers/</guid>
      <description>Video Materials&#xA;Access Modifiers in Python Most of the content below will apply to the Java language only. Python does not directly support information hiding through access modifiers, but simulates it by allowing developers to prefix variables with underscores to indicate that they are “protected” and should be left alone. Likewise, prefixing a Python variable or method name with two underscores will make it appear private to the class, but a developer can simply add the class name to the variable or method name in order to access it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objects in Memory</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/10-objects-in-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/10-objects-in-memory/</guid>
      <description>We often talk about the class as a blueprint for an object. This is because classes define what properties and methods an object should have, in the form of a constructor. Consider this class representing a planet:&#xA;​ Java Python public class Planet{ private double mass; public double getMass(){ return this.mass; } private double radius; public double getRadius(){ return this.radius; } public Planet(double mass, double radius){ this.mass = mass; this.radius = radius; } } class Planet @property def mass(self) -&gt; float: return self.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Message Passing</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/11-message-passing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/11-message-passing/</guid>
      <description>Video Materials&#xA;The second criteria Alan Kay set for object-oriented languages was message passing. Message passing is a way to request a unit of code engage in a behavior, i.e. changing its state, or sharing some aspect of its state.&#xA;Consider the real-world analogue of a letter sent via the postal service. Such a message consists of: an address the message needs to be sent to, a return address, the message itself (the letter), and any data that needs to accompany the letter (the enclosures).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/12-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/12-summary/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter, we looked at how object-orientation adopted the concept of encapsulation to combine related state and behavior within a single unit of code, known as a class. We further explored how objects are instances of a class created through invoking a constructor method.&#xA;We also discussed several different ways of looking at and reasoning about objects - as a state machine, and as structured data stored in memory. We discussed how a method is really a form of message passing that provides an interface to interact with objects safely.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>