<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Releases :: CC 410 Textbook</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/</link><description>In this example project, we’ll explore taking an existing project and preparing it for release. We’ll then create the actual release package and upload them to GitHub along with a release tag.
The next page will discuss the overall requirements that this example project should include. After that, there is a page for each programming language with some basic steps and a video to walk you through the whole process.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assignment Requirements</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/01-requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/01-requirements/</guid><description>This page lists the example project requirements for Example 10 in CC 410. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.
Purpose This example will cover some concepts related to parallel programming. This is meant to be an exploratory project only, so requirements are very loose.
General Requirements No style or documentation requirements will be enforced for this example. Assignment Requirements This one is simple - follow the steps to create a proper release package for this project, and then upload it to GitHub as part of a release.</description></item><item><title>Java</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/02-java/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/02-java/</guid><description>Outline Here is a basic outline of the steps to follow to complete this example.
Clone Starter Code from GitHub git clone &lt;url> java Install SDKMAN Instructions
curl -s "https://get.sdkman.io" | bash Close and Reopen Terminal to load SDK Man
Install Gradle
sdk install gradle 7.6 Compile, Run &amp; Test Existing Project cd java gradle run gradle check Confirm that project runs and has no style errors.
See the textbook or video for steps to create a release.</description></item><item><title>Python</title><link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/02-python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/10-releases/02-python/</guid><description>Outline Here is a basic outline of the steps to follow to complete this example.
Clone Starter Code from GitHub git clone &lt;url> python Run Project cd python python3 -m src Install Tox pip3 install tox Check &amp; Test Existing Project python3 -m tox Confirm that project runs and has no style errors.
See the textbook or video for steps to create a release.
When complete, use Git to commit and push updated code.</description></item></channel></rss>