<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assignment Requirements :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/05-debugging-logging/01-requirements/index.html</link>
    <description>This page lists the example project requirements for Example 5 in CC 410. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose This example will cover debugging errors in a couple of existing projects.&#xA;General Requirements This milestone must follow these professional coding standards:&#xA;All code must be object-oriented. All executable code must be within a class Python package files such as __init__.py and __main__.py are exempt. Classes must be organized into packages based on common usage. This project must include automation for compilation, unit testing, documentation generation, and execution. Java: Use Gradle with the application plugin. The project should compile without errors. You may include a main class in a separate package for testing purposes only. Python: Use tox configured to use Python 3.10 and a requirements file to install libraries. You may include a main class in a separate package for testing purposes only. All code must properly compile or be interpreted. Java: It must compile using Gradle. Python: It must be interpreted using Python 3.10. Where specified, type hints should be included in the code, and all code should pass a strict Mypy type check. Submissions to Canvas should be tagged GitHub releases that are numbered according to Semantic Versioning. Unenforced requirements (click to expand): The following requirements ARE NOT enforced for this milestone:</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/z-examples/05-debugging-logging/01-requirements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>