<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/index.html</link>
    <description>Welcome to CC 410!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:49:46 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Course Introduction</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/01-introduction/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/01-introduction/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Previous Versions Video Script Hello and welcome to the Computational Core program!&#xA;My name is Russ Feldhausen, and I’ll be one of the instructors for this program. My contact information is shown here, and is also listed on the syllabus&#xA;[Slide 2]&#xA;There are many other instructors and TAs for this program that you may interact with or see in the tutorial videos. They all have been instrumental in the development of this program. Specifically, I’d like to recognize the work of Nathan Bean, the developer of the CIS 400 course on which this course is based.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Canvas &amp; Codio</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/02-navigating-canvas-codio/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/02-navigating-canvas-codio/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Codio Documentation Video Script This course makes extensive use of several features of Canvas which you may or may not have worked with before. To give you the best experience in this course, this video will briefly describe those features and the best way to access them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to Find Help</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/03-where-to-find-help/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/03-where-to-find-help/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides K-State IT Help Desk - Email helpdesk@ksu.edu K-State Online Canvas Help Instructure Canvas Guides Codio Documentation Codio Support K-State Libraries K-State CS Support K-State CS Advising K-State Engineering Student Services K-State Office of Student Life K-State Report It Video Script As you work on the materials in this course, you may run into questions or problems and need assistance. This video reviews the various types of help available to you in this course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Learn Programming</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/05-how-to-learn-programming/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/05-how-to-learn-programming/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides The Science of Learning Programming from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 Textbook The Power of Believing You Can Improve | Carol Dweck - TED Talk on Mindsets and the Power of “Yet” The New Science of Learning: How to Learn in Haromony with your Brain by Terry Doyle and Todd Zakrajsek - Great Book on Learning Constructivism on Wikipedia - Article about Jean Piaget’s Learning Philosophy Toward a Developmental Epistemology of Computer Programming by Raymond Lister - Introduces the Stages of Learning to Program Video Script Before we launch into the course itself, I wanted to take a few minutes to share some information with you regarding what we know about how students learn to program. This isn’t just anecdotal evidence from computer science teachers like me, but theories and research from education researchers who study how humans learn new skills and abilities throughout their lives.If I had to summarize all of this information in as few words as possible, I’d simply say “do the work.” Learning to program is difficult, and the only way to really get good at it is through constant practice and learning. However, that greatly oversimplifies the information that I want to share, and I’m hoping that you’ll find some helpful takeaways from this video that you can incorporate into your learning process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2025 Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/06-syllabus/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/06-syllabus/index.html</guid>
      <description>CC 410 - Advanced Programming - Fall 2025 Previous Versions&#xA;Instructor Contact Information Instructor: Mr. Russell Feldhausen (russfeld AT ksu DOT edu) Office: DUE 2213, but I mostly work remotely from Kansas City, MO Phone: (785) 292-3121 (Call/Text) Website: https://russfeld.me Virtual Office Hours: By appointment via Zoom. Book time to meet with me Preferred Methods of Communication: Email: Students should email cc410-help (cc410-help@KSUemailProd.onmicrosoft.com). We will try to respond within one business day. Ed Discussion: For short questions and discussions of course content and assignments, Ed Discussion is preferred since questions can be asked once and answered for all students. Students are encouraged to post questions there and use that space for discussion, and the instructor will strive to answer questions there as well. Phone/Text: Emergencies only! We will do our best to respond as quickly as we can. Prerequisites CC 310 - Data Structures &amp; Algorithms I (taken on or after Fall 2024) CC 315 - Data Structures &amp; Algorithms II (taken prior to Fall 2024) Course Overview Advanced programming techniques and projects. Concepts from object oriented programming, inheritance and polymorphism. GUI programming and event-driven programming. Software development methodologies, processes, and design patterns. Practical experience with professional communication and collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plagiarism Policy</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/07-plagiarism/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/07-plagiarism/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources K-State Honor &amp; Integrity System Video Script “On my honor, as a student, I have neither given nor received unauthorized aid on this academic work.” - K-State Honor Pledge&#xA;Plagiarism is a very serious concern in this course, and something that we do not take lightly. Computer programs and code are especially easy targets for plagiarism due to how easy it is to copy and manipulate code in such a way that it is unrecognizable as the original source but still performs correctly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codio Projects</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/08-codio-projects/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/00-introduction/08-codio-projects/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Video Script At this point, you should have completed the “Hello Real World” example project. This module contains GitHub Classroom assignments and Codio projects for the rest of this course. In this video, I’ll briefly explain what these are for and how they work. As always, if you have any questions or are unsure what to do, contact the instructors via cc410-help for assistance.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>