




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debugging &amp; Logging on CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debugging &amp; Logging on CC 410 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art of Debugging</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/02-art-of-debugging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/02-art-of-debugging/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
First, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly discuss the art of debugging. Finding and fixing bugs in a complex piece of software is indeed an art, meaning that it something that takes a great amount of skill that comes with practice. So, how can we get better at this? Here are some tips. Much of this content was inspired by the talk The Art of Debugging by Remy Sharp.
Write Fewer Bugs This seems pretty obvious, but as we&amp;rsquo;ve discussed several times in this course, software bugs can be very costly to fix, and the longer they remain in the source code, the harder they can be to fix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspecting State</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/03-inspecting-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/03-inspecting-state/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
Object in our object-oriented programs can really be thought of as two different parts - the state and behavior of the object. When debugging, we may need to consider both parts of the object to determine what is really going on behind the scenes. So, let&amp;rsquo;s look at some ways we can explore the state of our program.
Print Statement Debugging The quickest and easiest way to explore the state of our program at any particular point during its execution is to simply add a print statement that prints the value of any variables we are interested in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debuggers</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/05-debuggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/05-debuggers/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
What if we want to have a bit more control over our programs and use a more powerful tool for finding bugs. In that case, we&amp;rsquo;ll need to use a debugger. A debugger is a special application that allows us to inspect another program while it is running. Using a debugger, we can inspect both the state and behavior of an application, and observe the program directly while it runs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/01-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/01-introduction/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve already spent quite a bit of time learning how to write code for our programs. But, what if something goes wrong? How can we fix it?
Unfortunately, it is nearly impossible to write a computer program that doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain any bugs. In fact, it is a common joke among programmers that the only truly bug-free program you&amp;rsquo;ll ever write is the classic &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; program! So, we&amp;rsquo;ll need to have some tools at our disposal that we can use to find and fix the various bugs or errors in our code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspecting Behavior</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/04-inspecting-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/04-inspecting-behavior/</guid>
      <description>We may also wish to inspect the behavior of our program that could lead to a particular error. Specifically, we may need to know what set of function calls and classes lead to the error itself. In that case, we&amp;rsquo;ll need a way to see what code was executed before the bug was reached.
Stack Trace One of the most useful ways to inspect the behavior of our application is to look at the call stack or stack trace of the program when it reaches an exception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logging</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/06-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/06-logging/</guid>
      <description>The last major concept we&amp;rsquo;ll introduce around debugging is the use of a formal logger in our code. A logger allows us to collect debugging information throughout our program in a way that is lightweight, highly configurable, and surprisingly easy to use. Both Java and Python include some standard ways to create a simple log file.
Java Python Java Logger The Java language includes the Logger class that can be used to create a logger within the code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/07-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/07-debugging-logging/07-summary/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter, we discussed some steps we can take when debugging our applications. When we find a bug, we should try to figure out how to replicate it first, then focus on isolating the bug, and finally fix the bug. While we do so, we can write additional unit tests to reproduce the bug that will help us confirm that we&amp;rsquo;ve fixed it, and we can perform some regression testing to make sure we didn&amp;rsquo;t introduce any new errors.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>