




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design Patterns on CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design Patterns on CC 410 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Gang of Four</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/02-gang-of-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/02-gang-of-four/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
1
While the first discussions of patterns in software architecture occurred much earlier, the concept was popularized in 1994 with the publication of Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software by Erich Gamma, Richard Helm, Ralph Johnson, and John Vlissides. Collectively, the four authors of this book have been referred to as the &amp;ldquo;Gang of Four&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;GoF&amp;rdquo; within the software development community, so it is common to see references to that name when discussing the particular software design patterns discussed in the book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Builder Pattern</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/04-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/04-builder/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
The first pattern we&amp;rsquo;ll look at is the builder pattern. The builder pattern is used to simplify building complex objects, where the class that needs the object shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to include all of the code and details for how to construct that object. By decoupling the code for constructing the complex object from the classes that use it, it becomes much simpler to change the representations or usages of the complex object without changing the classes that use it, provided they all adhere to the same general API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterator Pattern</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/07-iterator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/07-iterator/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
Let&amp;rsquo;s review three other commonly used software design patterns. These are either patterns that we&amp;rsquo;ve seen before, or ones that we might end up using soon in our code.
Iterator Pattern The first pattern is the iterator pattern. The iterator pattern is a behavioral pattern that is used to traverse through a collection of objects stored in a container. We explored this pattern in several of the data structures introduced in earlier data structures courses such as CC 310 and CC 315, as well as CIS 300.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapter Pattern</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/08-adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/08-adapter/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video
Video Materials
Another pattern is the adapter pattern. The adapter pattern is a structural pattern that is used to make an existing interface fit within a different interface. Just like we might use an adapter when traveling abroad to allow our appliances to plug in to different electrical outlets around the world, the adapter pattern lets us use one interface in place of another, similar interface.
1
In the UML diagram above, we see two different approaches to using the adapter pattern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/01-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/01-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Up to this point, we&amp;rsquo;ve mainly been developing our programs without any underlying patterns between them. Each program is custom-written to fit the particular situation or use case, and beyond using a few standard data structures, the code and structure within each program is mostly unique to that application. In this chapter, we&amp;rsquo;re going to learn about software design patterns, a very powerful aspect of object-oriented programming and a way that we can write code that is more easily recognized and understood by other developers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Design Patterns</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/03-software-design-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/03-software-design-patterns/</guid>
      <description>The most important part of the book by the &amp;ldquo;Gang of Four,&amp;rdquo; as evidenced by the title, are the 23 software design patterns that are discussed within the book.
A software design pattern is a reusable structure or solution to a common problem or usage within software development. Throughout the course of developing many different programs in the object-oriented paradigm, developers may find that they are reusing similar ideas or code structures within applications with completely different uses, which leads to the idea of formalizing these ideas into reusable structures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Method Pattern</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/05-factory-method/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/05-factory-method/</guid>
      <description>The next pattern we&amp;rsquo;ll explore is the factory method pattern. The factory method pattern is used to allow us to construct an object of a desired type without actually having to specify that type explicitly in our code. Instead, we just provide the factory with an input specifying the type of object we need, and it will return an instance of that type. By making use of the factory method pattern, classes that require access to these object don&amp;rsquo;t need to be updated any time an underlying object type is modified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singleton Pattern</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/06-singleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/06-singleton/</guid>
      <description>Finally, let&amp;rsquo;s look at one other common creational pattern: the singleton pattern. The singleton pattern is a simple pattern that allows a program to enforce the limitation that there is only a single instance of a class in use within the entire program. So, when another class needs an instance of this class, instead of instantiating a new one, it will simply get a reference to the single existing object. This allows the entire program to share a single instance of an object, and that instance can be used to coordinate actions across the entire system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Template Method Pattern</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/09-template-method/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/09-template-method/</guid>
      <description>The last pattern we&amp;rsquo;ll review in this course is the template method pattern. The template method pattern is a pattern that is used to define the outline or skeleton of a method in an abstract parent class, while leaving the actual details of the implementation to the subclasses that inherit from the parent class. In this way, the parent class can enforce a particular structure or ordering of the steps performed in the method, making sure that any subclass will behave similarly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/10-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/09-design-patterns/10-summary/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter, we explored several software design patterns introduced by the &amp;ldquo;Gang of Four&amp;rdquo; in their 1994 book: Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software. Design patterns are a great way to build our code using reusable, standard structures that can solve a particular problem or perform a particular task. By using structures that are familiar to other developers, it makes it easier for them to understand our code.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>