




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Updates on CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weekly Updates on CC 410 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 10:53:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week01/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week one Announcements video for CC 410 in Spring 2023, my name is Russell Feldhausen. And I&amp;rsquo;ll be your instructor this semester. My contact information is here on the slide, you can email me anytime you can also contact me, I generally work remotely, I usually am at home in Shawnee, Kansas near Kansas City. But I&amp;rsquo;m usually on campus on Mondays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week02/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to week two of CC 410 in spring 2023. So today you should be wrapping up module one, which includes the Hello real world project. And it also includes the first final project meeting. So if you haven&amp;rsquo;t done that already, please schedule a time to meet with me via Calendly. Over the next week or so, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk a little bit about the final project in this class, it gives us a chance to get to know each other, and it opens up that line of communication as you work on your final project throughout the rest of the semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week03/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023, this week you should be wrapping up module two, which is all about object oriented programming. There was an example project that went with that and you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be wrapping up the first restaurant milestone, we&amp;rsquo;re really setting the stage for the project that we&amp;rsquo;re going to work on throughout the rest of the semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week04/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week for announcements video for cc 410 in spring 2023. This week, you should have wrapped up the module on documentation unit testing and creating UML diagrams for your project. There&amp;rsquo;s also an example and then the second restaurant milestone that&amp;rsquo;s all about adding testing and documentation to your restaurant project. Hopefully, you&amp;rsquo;ve got all of those turned in by now, and I&amp;rsquo;ll work on getting them graded later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week05/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week five Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023. This week you should be wrapping up the module on inheritance and polymorphism. There&amp;rsquo;s an example project there. There&amp;rsquo;s also a Start Stop continue survey that I&amp;rsquo;d like you to fill out just gives me some quick feedback in the middle of the semester. If there&amp;rsquo;s anything you&amp;rsquo;d like me to start doing, stop doing, or make sure I continue doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 6</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week06/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week six Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023. This week you should be wrapping up the last modules on debugging and logging and lambda expressions. There&amp;rsquo;s an example project that was due last week. And then right now you should be working on the third restaurant milestone, a lot of which is about adding inheritance and polymorphism into our existing project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 7</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week07/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week seven Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023. This week you&amp;rsquo;re working on the last of the two new modules that we&amp;rsquo;re working on this one covers test doubles, also known as mocks, you&amp;rsquo;ll be doing an example project around that. And in your work, you&amp;rsquo;re working on the fifth restaurant milestone, which we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about in a minute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 8</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week08/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week eight announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023, so this week, you should be wrapping up the module on test doubles and mock objects, which is one of the other new units we&amp;rsquo;ve added this semester. You also should have met with me last week probably for the final project. And then you should have completed the first concept quiz in this class, which was due late last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week09/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week nine Announcements video for CC 410 In spring 2023. This week we&amp;rsquo;re going to go through a couple of different examples. The first one is about parallel programming, which is an important concept for us to learn when working with user interfaces. We&amp;rsquo;ll also do an example around event driven programming, which allows us to make our interfaces interactive. And then finally, we&amp;rsquo;ll have another milestone for the restaurant project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 10</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week10/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 10 Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023. This week we&amp;rsquo;re going to be working on an external libraries example where we&amp;rsquo;ll talk a little bit more about how we can add code from external sources into our program. Then you work on the eighth milestone in the restaurant project where we&amp;rsquo;ll add some new features. And finally, you&amp;rsquo;ll be asked to do a Start Stop continue survey, which is just your chance to give me some quick feedback as we go through the semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 11</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week11/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 11 Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023. My apologies for being a little bit behind this week, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to get this video out on Thursday. This week, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be looking at releases, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk a little bit about how we can actually build a releasable version of our project. So we&amp;rsquo;ll do a quick example around that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 12</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week12/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 12 Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2023. This week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to shift gears a little bit and start working on a web graphical user interface instead of a traditional desktop user interface.
So we&amp;rsquo;re going to start working with data driven websites. Mainly, we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to install a website framework into our existing projects and how to configure that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring `23 Week 13</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week13/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 13 Announcements video for CC 410 In spring 2023. This week, you should continue working on the milestones around adding a web interface to your project. This week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to deal with rest, which is a really important concept in web interfaces. And you&amp;rsquo;ll also learn how to create some forms and deal with form data. And then that all comes together to the restaurant project where you&amp;rsquo;re going to add a form where you can create a custom item and add it to your restaurants menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 14</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week14/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 14 Announcements video for CC 410 in Spring 2023, as you can see, I&amp;rsquo;ve got the green screen behind me, I&amp;rsquo;m getting ready to record some new videos for some other classes. So this week, you should be working on your fourth Final Project milestone, which is talking about ways you&amp;rsquo;re going to integrate libraries and API&amp;rsquo;s. So make sure you&amp;rsquo;re scheduling that meeting with me over the next week or so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;23 Week 15</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week15/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 15 Announcements video for CC 410 In spring 2023. So recently, you should have completed the second concept quiz in this class, which goes over a lot of the stuff that we&amp;rsquo;ve learned in the second half of the class, you also should have completed the rest example. And you should have completed the 12th restaurant milestone, which is about adding a RESTful API into your project itself.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>