




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Updates on CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weekly Updates on CC 410 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 10:53:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week01/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2022. My name is Russ, I&amp;rsquo;ll be your instructor for the semester, I&amp;rsquo;ll probably post these announcements videos about once a week, usually on Tuesdays since I&amp;rsquo;m on campus on Mondays and won&amp;rsquo;t have time to record them. So you can check Canvas about every Tuesday to get a quick update for me on what you&amp;rsquo;re doing this week and anything else that&amp;rsquo;s on my mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week02/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week two announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. So you should be wrapping up module one this week, which includes the Hello real world project and the first final project meeting. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t done that already, please take a minute to schedule a time to meet with me using my Calendly link. So we can talk about the final project in this class and just answer any questions you might have about what&amp;rsquo;s going on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week03/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week you should be wrapping up module two, which is all about object oriented programming. You&amp;rsquo;ve also got a quick example on object oriented programming. And you&amp;rsquo;re also going to be diving deep into the first restaurant milestone. Hopefully all of that is going well. But if you have any questions or concerns, feel free to let me know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week04/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week for announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2022. This week, you should be wrapping up the documentation and testing portion of the class as well as the portion that deals with UML. There&amp;rsquo;s an example all about documentation and testing in your code. And then the second restaurant milestone is all about adding a lot of unit tests and documentation directly to the code that you wrote for the first milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week05/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week five Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week you should be wrapping up the module on inheritance and polymorphism. There&amp;rsquo;s also an example that goes along with that. But there&amp;rsquo;s not a milestone due this week. You also should have gotten the start stop continue survey, I&amp;rsquo;ve received several responses already. And I&amp;rsquo;ve responded to some of those in an announcement on Canvas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 6</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week06/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week six Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week, you should be wrapping up the last part of the first section of the course, which deals with debugging and logging. You&amp;rsquo;ll also learn about Lambda expressions. And you&amp;rsquo;ll be working on the third restaurant milestone where you&amp;rsquo;re adding a whole lot of inheritance and polymorphism into your project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 7</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week07/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week seven announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2022, this week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to switch gears a little bit and spend some time working on both parallel programming and event driven programming, a couple of different paradigms that you&amp;rsquo;ve maybe seen before, but you haven&amp;rsquo;t worked with a little bit. So this will be some really good examples that you can work through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 8</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week08/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week eight announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to be starting on what I think is one of the most important chapters in this class where we learn both about design patterns, which are really useful ways that you can solve common problems in your code in a very structured way that other developers will recognize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week09/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week nine Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week, you should have wrapped up a module on design patterns and test doubles as well as done an example around that. This week, all you&amp;rsquo;re going to be doing is working on restaurant milestone six, which is one of the two really big milestones in this class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 10</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week10/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 10 Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022 This week and next week, you should still be working on the external libraries and releases examples. And then you also have a restaurant milestone all about checking out, which is what we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about today.
So milestone seven, it really can be split into two parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 11</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week11/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 11 Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022, this week you should be working on milestone seven. And you&amp;rsquo;ll also have a short example on creating a release. Those are really the only big topics for this week, you also should be finishing up the external libraries example from last week if you haven&amp;rsquo;t done that already.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 12</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week12/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 12 Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week we&amp;rsquo;re switching gears from working in the traditional graphical user interfaces. And now we&amp;rsquo;re going to start working on web interfaces. So this week, you&amp;rsquo;re going to have some examples on building data driven websites using either Python or Java, you&amp;rsquo;ll go through the basics of adding a web framework into your existing project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 13</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week13/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 13 Announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2022 This week you should be working on the second of the web milestones. This one you&amp;rsquo;re going to learn about restful API&amp;rsquo;s and also about Web Forms. You&amp;rsquo;ll do an example around using form data to search through the movies collection. And then the milestone will be to create a search form for the items in the menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;22 Week 14</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week14/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 14 Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2022. This week you should be wrapping up your fourth Final Project milestone which is involved, just meeting with me and making sure that your final project is on track to be done by the end of the semester. The second concept quiz is also done due this Friday. So make sure you can set aside about three hours to work on that.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>