<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Updates :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/index.html</link>
    <description>Information for Current Students!&#xA;Previous Semesters Are Here</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 09:49:47 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;25 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week01/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week01/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements video for CC410 in fall 2025. Welcome to a new semester. My name is Russ Feldhausen. I’ll be your instructor this semester. My contact information is here. It’s on the syllabus. It’s on the Canvas homepage. It’s in the introductory video. Hopefully you can easily find a way to get a hold of me. Please be aware that I work remotely out of Kansas City most of the week, so I won’t be available on campus. I do come to campus on Mondays. So if you want to meet with me in person, Mondays in the morning is probably your best bet to do that. But since this is an online course, I’m guessing most of you might be online as well. And so I should actually be really easy to reach either via email, Ed Discussion, Teams, Discord, whatever you want to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;25 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week02/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week02/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week to announcements video for CC410 in fall 2025. So this week you should be wrapping up the first module which includes the Hello Real World project. I really like the Hello Real World project because I think it takes the classic Hello World project that you start with and really expands upon it in a way that makes it match more what you’d see in the real world with things like type checking and unit testing and all of these other things that we’re going to do in this class. So hopefully you’re getting that wrapped up and getting that committed and pushed to GitHub so that we can get that graded. As always, if you have any questions with that, let me know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;25 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week03/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week03/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements for CC410 in fall 2025. So, this week you should be wrapping up the second module, which I believe the milestone for that is due pretty soon. So, make sure you get that turned in. You’ll be doing the example for that, and you’ll be doing the first restaurant milestone. For this first restaurant milestone, I will try and give pretty detailed feedback, usually within a day or two of getting it submitted. So I’m hoping to work on that either today or tomorrow of this week. I also will give you feedback on your Hello Real World project. I haven’t had time to get to that yet because we had some other things going on this semester, but I will get you feedback pretty quickly for your first restaurant milestone so you can roll that into your second milestone, which will be new next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;25 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week04/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week04/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week four announcements video for CC410 in fall 2025. This week you should be wrapping up the next module, which is on documentation, testing, and creating a UML diagram for your project. You’re going to do a quick example where you add documentation and unit testing to an example project. And then you’re going to be working on the second restaurant project, which is all about adding documentation and unit testing to your restaurant project. That milestone can be pretty big, but hopefully it goes well. If you have any questions about unit tests you should be adding, please let me know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;25 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week05/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/week05/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for CC410 in fall 2025. This week you should be wrapping up a module on inheritance and polymorphism and playing around with an example on inheritance. Also in this week, we’ve got a start, stop, continue survey, which I think is one of the really important things I want you to get through in this class. So please take a little bit to work on that. That just gives me some quick feedback on how things are going. And hopefully you’ve got a little time to work on the final project because we’re working on a two-week module. There’s going to be a little bit of gap in there. So hopefully you can start working on some final project time as well.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>