<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>




	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			
			
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			

	
	
			
			
			

	
	
			

	
	
			
			

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fall 2021 on CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fall 2021 on CC 410 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CC 310 &amp; 315 Cover</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/cc310-315/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/cc310-315/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Greetings to students in CC 310 and CC 315. My name is Russell Feldhausen. And I&amp;rsquo;ll be covering for Emily this week while she is out of the office. My contact information is here Feel free to get in touch with me if you have any questions. Basically, everything should be pretty much the same this week as normal. If you need any help, please email the course email help address that is cc310-help or cc315-help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week01/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week one announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2021. My name is Russell Feldhausen. And I&amp;rsquo;ll be your instructor this semester. My contact information is here on the screen, you can also find it on the syllabus, I&amp;rsquo;m email is by far my preferred communication method. In this course, there is a special course communication email that&amp;rsquo;s listed on the syllabus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week02/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week two announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2021, so this week today should be wrapping up module one and the Hello real world project. Those are both due today, make sure the Hello real world project that you get your submission posted on GitHub, and then send me the link for the release tag that you make in GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week03/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2021, so you should be wrapping up at this point, the second module. So we have object oriented programming and the example. And then you also should be submitting the first milestone for the restaurant project. So hopefully that went well, it was a lot of building classes and objects in your code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week04/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 4 announcements for CC 410 in Fall 2021. So this week, you should be wrapping up the second restaurant milestone, which is all about documentation, unit testing and using UML diagrams to show us the structure of your program. Hopefully, that&amp;rsquo;s all going well, it&amp;rsquo;s all due tonight. So make sure you get that submitted online. As always, I&amp;rsquo;ll try and go through and grade it sometime tomorrow and give you really good feedback on canvas and GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week05/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week five video for CC 410 in Fall 2021. So this week, you should be wrapping up the third module, which is all on inheritance and polymorphism. And starting to work on refactoring your code to take advantage of some of that. So right now, the chapter on inheritance and polymorphism is due. And the example is due. The next milestone, which is milestone three is not due until next week, so you&amp;rsquo;ve got an extra week to work on that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 6</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week06/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week six announcements video for cc 410 in Fall 2021. So this week you should be wrapping up the last part of the first chunk of the class, which is all about debugging and logging, lambda expressions. And you&amp;rsquo;re working on the third restaurant milestone which covers inheritance and polymorphism. So all of that is due later today. I&amp;rsquo;ll get that graded here in the next couple of days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week09/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2021. So we&amp;rsquo;re on week nine, I apologize for missing the last couple of weeks. I was on vacation two weeks ago. And then last week, I was busy getting caught up with everything, but we&amp;rsquo;re back on track and you should see announcements videos for most of the rest of the semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 10</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week10/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 10 Announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2021. So this week you&amp;rsquo;re working on milestone seven, which is the checkout milestone, you&amp;rsquo;ll have two weeks to work on that. This week, you&amp;rsquo;re also doing an example on external libraries, which is really interesting. And then next week, you&amp;rsquo;ll work on actually creating a packaged and installable release of your software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;21 Week 12</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2021/week12/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Video Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 12 Announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2021. So this week, we&amp;rsquo;ll be pivoting from working on our graphical user interfaces to starting working on the web. And so the example this week, we&amp;rsquo;ll introduce you to web frameworks and how you can build data driven websites using the same set of code that we&amp;rsquo;ve been using throughout this semester.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>