




  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spring 2022 :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week01/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to CC 410. My name is Russ Feldhausen. And I’ll be your instructor this semester, I’m going to try and do weekly announcements videos like this about once a week or maybe once every other week, just to give you some updates about what’s going on in the class. These videos are unscripted, they’re not going to be nearly as produced as the rest of the videos in the class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week02/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week two announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So by this point this week, you should have wrapped up module one, which is all about the Hello real world project and all of the introductory stuff for the course. Hopefully by now you’ve also scheduled your first final project meeting with me, mainly, what we’ll do is just go over the final project, discuss any finer points that you might be interested in and maybe discuss possible topics that you can think about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week03/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up the second module in the class, which is all about object oriented programming. And so if you’re seeing this on Monday, by the end of today, you should have the object oriented programming example done, and you should be submitting the first milestone for your restaurant project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week04/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week for announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up the second restaurant milestone, which is all about documentation and unit testing, you should have done an example and then you’ll add a lot of documentation and unit tests as well as a UML diagram to your restaurant project. Hopefully, that’s going well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week05/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. You get to see me in my professional recording setup because I’m recording some videos today for CC 110. And I figured I’d do some videos for CC 410 as well.&#xA;So this week, you should be wrapping up module four, which is all about inheritance and polymorphism. There’s also an example project that you’re going through, and you should have a start stop continue survey to fill out, please do fill out that survey, I do get some really good feedback from that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 6</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week06/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week six announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week, you should be wrapping up the module on debugging, logging and, lambda expressions and be working on the milestone where you’re adding all of the inheritance and polymorphism into your restaurant project. Hopefully, that’s going okay. If you have any questions, I’ll be available today to answer questions via email or on Discord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 7</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week07/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week seven announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week, we’ll be doing the second module on GUI programming, which is all about event driven programming. And so in this module, you’ll actually have two smaller examples covering both parallel programming and event driven programming. And then you’ll work on the fifth restaurant milestone, which is all about making your GUI reactive to button clicks and things like that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 8</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week08/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week eight announcements video for CC 410 in Spring 2022. So this week coming up is spring break. So we’re talking about things that are happening after spring break. This is one of the larger modules where this week you’ll be covering things like design patterns and test doubles, you might also know them as mock objects. And so this whole milestone is about a lot of cool programming concepts that are related to object oriented programming, but help extend your ability to develop programs that people can understand and to develop your ability to write unit tests that can actually test around those objects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week09/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So we’re just getting back from spring break, and you’re still working on the same module as before. So this week, you’ll be working on design patterns and test doubles. And you’ll also have an example around using patterns and test doubles or mocks in your projects. And then you’ll start working on milestone six, you have two weeks to work on milestone six.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 10</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week10/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 10 Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week next week, you’ll be working on milestone seven in the restaurant project, which is all about including external libraries and getting ready for complete release, we’re also going to be adding the GUI panels that we need to actually modify combos in our project.&#xA;So milestone seven, this is the biggest most complicated milestone in the class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 11</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week11/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 11 Announcements video in CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week, you should be finishing up milestone seven, which is all about checkout. And you’ll also be doing a quick example on building a release of your project. This is a really great opportunity to learn how to package your software up in a way that other people can use it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 12</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week12/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 12 Announcements video for CC 410 in Spring 2022. So this week, hopefully you should be wrapping up the milestone on checkout and getting all of that working. It’s by far the most complex milestone in the course. So hopefully that’s going well. But if you still have questions, feel free to contact me today, and I’ll do my best to answer your questions throughout today until it’s due tonight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 14</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week14/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the Week 14 Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. So this week, you should be scheduling your fourth and final final project meeting with me, we’re going to talk a little bit about using external libraries and API’s and generally just checking to see where you’re at on the project and make sure you’re making good progress. Because we’re getting really close to the end of the semester, you’ll also be continuing to work on the restaurant project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;22 Week 15</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2022/week15/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 15 Announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2022. This is the last announcements video, I won’t be doing a video on finals week. So we’re going to cover everything you need to know for the end of this semester in this video. First and foremost due today is the second concept quiz in the course, so make sure that you go through that and get that submitted, it does take a little bit of time, I think you’re allocated about two or two and a half hours to work on that it should be more than enough time to get through it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>