




  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spring &amp; Summer 2021 :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Final Project</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/00-final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/00-final-project/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for the Final Project in CC 410. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose This assignment allow students to exercise their programming skills by building a project of their own design. Ideally, the project will be something related to the student’s personal interests or area of study. All the requirements listed below are considered flexible and can be adapted to fit the individual project and student.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Real World</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/00-hello-real-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/00-hello-real-world/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for the Example 1 - Hello Real World project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose This assignment mimics the traditional “Hello World” project that most programmers learn as their first program, but done following professional coding standards and guidelines. In effect, this is how a professional coder would write “Hello World” as a project for work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant Classes</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/01-restaurant-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/01-restaurant-classes/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 1 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;This first milestone involves building the classes that represent items on the restaurant’s menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentation &amp; Testing</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/02-documentation-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/02-documentation-testing/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 2 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The second milestone involves writing documentation and unit tests for our existing code base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inheritance</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/03-inheritance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/03-inheritance/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 3 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The third milestone involves refactoring our code to take advantage of inheritance and the use of interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUI Basics</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/04-gui-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/04-gui-basics/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 4 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The fourth milestone involves creating the various GUI windows and panels required for this project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-Driven Programming</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/05-event-driven-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/05-event-driven-programming/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 5 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The fifth milestone involves dealing with the various events generated by the GUI and constructing a list of items that represent an order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders &amp; Combos</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/06-orders-combos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/06-orders-combos/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 6 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The sixth milestone involves creating combo meals and orders from the items selected in the GUI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checkout</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/07-checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/07-checkout/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 7 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The seventh milestone involves finalizing the GUI for creating combos, and handling the steps to check out and pay for an order, including printing a receipt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Basics</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/08-website-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/08-website-basics/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 8 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The eighth milestone involves moving into the web by creating a data-driven website to display the menu and some other information about the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form Data</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/09-form-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/09-form-data/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 9 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The ninth milestone involves augmenting the menu display from the previous project by adding search and filtering functionality via an HTML form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESTful Architecture</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/10-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/10-rest/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 10 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The tenth milestone involves building a RESTful web application that could be used to manage custom menu items.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validation &amp; Serialization</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/11-validation-serialization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/y-milestones/old/spring-2021/11-validation-serialization/</guid>
      <description>This page lists the milestone requirements for Milestone 11 of the CC 410 Restaurant Project. Read the requirements carefully and discuss any questions with the instructors or TAs.&#xA;Purpose The CC 410 Restaurant Project project for this semester is centered around building a point of sale (POS) system for a fictional restaurant named Starfleet Subs, based in the Star Trek universe.&#xA;The eleventh milestone involves adding form validation and serialization to the existing project, specifically targeted at custom menu items.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>