<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fall 2024 :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/index.html</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week01/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week01/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to CC410. My name is Russell Feldhausen. My contact information is here on this slide. You can also find it on the syllabus and on the homepage on Canvas. I will be your instructor for the semester in the CC410 advanced programming course. So in this course the big picture is we’re going to cover a lot of programming topics including object oriented programming, unit testing, design patterns. We’re going to learn about building graphical user interfaces, web interfaces, and we’ll do some work with serialization. The way we’re going to do this is a lot of guided example projects where I will have longer form like 45 minute to an hour long videos where I do a smaller example of what you’re working on and then you’ll actually apply that by building out this point of sale system for a restaurant project. So you’ll do several milestones of this restaurant project and then throughout the semester you’ll also be thinking about and planning a final project that you’ll probably spend about the last four weeks of class working on but we’ll spend the whole semester actually thinking about it planning it and maybe getting some of the framework in place as you work on the restaurant project as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week02/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week02/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week two announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. This week you should be wrapping up the first module in the class which includes the Hello Real World example project. All you really have to do for that project is watch the video and follow along and then submit what you have gotten completed at the end of that. You also should have scheduled a meeting to meet with me for the first final project milestone so if you haven’t done that please make sure you do that this week. All we’re really going to do is chat about the final project in this class and give you a chance to ask any questions you might have. You don’t have to come up with a project or anything at this point. I just like to get you thinking about it now so that when we do get to the final project later in October you already have an idea that you’ve been thinking about and you’re ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week03/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week03/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week three announcements for CC410 in Fall 2023. So this week you should be wrapping up module two, which is on object oriented programming. There’s a small object oriented programming example where you’ll make a menu item for a fictional ice cream restaurant. And then you’ll be working on the first restaurant milestone where you’ll be making the object oriented classes for the menu of the restaurant project that you’ve chosen to work on. So after you’ve got that done this week, we’re going to go back to that code. We’re going to add some documentation and unit testing to it. We’re also going to create a UML diagram that oversees exactly how that code looks. So you’ll do a small example of adding documentation and unit testing to an existing project. And then you’ll go to the second restaurant milestone to do all of that work in your code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week04/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week04/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week four announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. So this week you should be wrapping up the second restaurant project milestone, which involves adding documentation, unit testing, and a UML diagram to your project. You should have done a short example of adding documentation and unit testing to an existing project, and then you’ll expand that into the restaurant project. And hopefully you’re getting that all done. I noticed that so far I’ve only got one of those submitted, so hopefully you’re getting that wrapped up and submitted pretty soon later today. So this week we’re going to shift gears a little bit, and we’ll spend some time talking about inheritance and polymorphism, which are two of the really big reasons that we use object oriented programming in this class. We’re going to do a small example of looking at inheritance, and then you’ll have some time to think about your project, but there won’t actually be a restaurant milestone due this week. There is one due next week that includes debugging and logging as well. And so instead this week you’ll have a little bit of time to think about your final project. There’s a start stop continue survey out there, which basically asks you if there’s anything I should start doing in this class, stop doing in this class, or anything I should continue doing if you like things that I do. So it’s a chance for you to give some feedback. But really the big thing for this module is get through this module pretty quick so you can go ahead to the next module and start looking at that content and start working on the milestone, because there is a reason that I give you two weeks to work on this milestone. So you want to get to that as soon as you can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week05/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week05/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week five announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. This week, you should be wrapping up the work on inheritance and polymorphism. There’s a short example project that you’re working on, but there shouldn’t be anything else. And so instead at the end of this module, I’ve added a start, stop, continue survey, which gives you a quick chance at the beginning of the semester to tell me if there’s anything I should change about my approach. And then you also have some final project time that you can work on as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 6</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week06/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week06/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week six announcements video for CC410 in fall 2024. So this week you should be wrapping up the modules on debugging, logging and Lambda expressions. There’s a small example that you do on debugging and logging and then the third restaurant milestone is due pretty soon. So make sure you get that done. You also should be scheduling your second final project meeting with me. So I look forward to hearing about some of your interests and things that you’re looking at for your final project. This is again, just a quick discussion to see where you’re at on project planning and maybe give you some advice of things that you could start working on in your final project as you have some time over the next few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 7</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week07/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week07/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the Week 7 Announcements video for CC410 in Fall 2024. This week, you should be working on a Restaurant Milestone all about adding test doubles, which allows us to add mock or fake objects into our unit tests so that we can better test those design patterns that we’ve been working on. This really allows us to write more powerful and more expressive unit tests, which are really useful for actually measuring how we’re going to use our project in the future. You also should be working on the first concept quiz in this class, which is due later this week. Again, please remember that concept quiz is open book, open notes, but not open chat GPT or anything like that. It’s really a chance for me to test your understanding and your knowledge of the answers. And it’s usually pretty obvious if the answers are like way off base and use words and concepts that we haven’t even covered in this class. So please make sure that it is your own work and it represents your own understanding of what’s going on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 8</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week08/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week08/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the Week 8 announcements video for CC410 in fall 2024. This week you should be wrapping up the module on test doubles. You should have also scheduled a meeting with me for your second final project milestone where we’ll talk a little bit more about final project ideas. And hopefully you should have also completed the first concept quiz, which goes over some of the big concepts in this class. I’m going to work on getting all of that graded this week. It may take me a couple of days to get through everything, but I’ll try and get you feedback as soon as I can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week09/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week09/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week 9 announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. I’m coming to you this week from my office on campus because I’m on the road a little bit so hopefully the quality of the video is not too bad and I can at least get the point across. So this week you should be working on a module all about parallel programming and doing an example of doing parallel programming in either language that you’re working on and then we’ll shift over and do some work with event driven programming which is the paradigm that we use a lot in graphical user interfaces. You’ll do an example around that and then you’ll be working on the seventh milestone in the restaurant project which adds some interactivity to your user interface that you built in the previous milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 10</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week10/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week10/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 10 announcements video for CC 410 in Fall 2024. This week we’re working on parallel programming, so you’ll do a short example around that. We’ll also work a little bit on event -driven programming, and you’ll do an example around that. And then you’ll work on the seventh restaurant milestone. This is the milestone where you’re going to add event -driven programming to your user interface so that you can actually switch between windows, you can save objects, and you can actually update the order itself. This is where we actually start building the real interactive part of the user interface by building these event -driven pieces of code into our GUI, and it hopefully really helps you understand a little bit better how we actually work in an event -driven scenario instead of an imperative scenario like you’ve worked at in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 11</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week11/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week11/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week 11 announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. This week you’re going to be working on an example around releases. We’re going to talk about how we can actually build a releasable version of our code that others can easily use. You’ll do a small example around building a release and then you’ll switch over to the restaurant project where you’re going to add an external library to help us actually go through the checkout process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 12</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week12/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week12/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week 12 announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. This week you should be working on data driven websites. We’re going to introduce how to build a website using our same framework and so this first milestone is just adding the basics for the website so that we can produce a menu on the website. We’re not going to handle ordering items or anything on the website, we’re just going to create a data driven menu. But really the idea for this week is we’re going to start backing off so you can work on the final project. So like I said the tenth milestone is pretty simple. We’re going to install a web framework inside of our existing project. We’re going to set up the routes in the controller for the web framework as well as some layout templates and some route templates and it’s going to allow us to build a web page that has the menu on it that is driven by our object oriented data that we already have. In practice when you do this with a website instead of having object oriented classes for your menu you would probably have a database but that’s outside the scope of this class so we’re just going to use our existing object oriented layout to drive our menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 13</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week13/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week13/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week 13 announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. This week you should be working on some more of the restaurant milestones. We’ve switched gears into the web milestones. So this week you’re going to add some restful interfaces and a form interface to your restaurant website. This form interface is going to allow you to add a custom menu item or a list of custom menu items to the menu. They’re not going to change the existing menu items. They’re just going to add custom information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 14</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week14/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week14/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week 14 announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. So this week you should be scheduling your final project check-in with me. This is the fourth final project milestone and the last one before you turn it in. So this is a last good chance to look at your final project and see how things going. We also have the second concept quiz that’s out and due this Friday so make sure that you get that done. As with the previous quiz it takes an hour or so to complete so make sure you schedule enough time for that. You’re also going to be working on an example project for restful routing and then the next restaurant milestone after Thanksgiving is also going to be about restful routing and so you should be working on that while you work on your final project as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall &#39;24 Week 15</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week15/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/fall-2024/week15/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the week 15 announcements video for CC 410 in fall 2024. So we are at the last week of the semester before finals so this week we’re going to work on our last restaurant milestone which is all about adding validation and some serialization to our web forms so hopefully that shouldn’t be too bad to get done it’s a usual usually a pretty short milestone and then other than that you should keep working on your final project which is due a week from this Friday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>