<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/ii-gui/15-releases/02-preparing-for-release/video/index.html</link>
    <description>Resources Slides Video Script In this chapter, we’re going to quickly discuss what it will take to package our application and create a release that others can easily download and use in their own applications. First, let’s talk about all the steps we might want to take to prepare our software for release. First and foremost, we should thoroughly test our software and make sure it is as free of bugs and errors as we can get. Having ample unit tests is very helpful at this point, and it can also help anyone who wants to help improve the application by giving them a quick and easy way to confirm that nothing is broken. In addition, you’ll want to take some time to document your code, both in code comments but also by creating some user documentation to help users understand how to best use the application. As you go through the code, you should try to clean up any unnecessary debugging or logging statements, either by commenting them out or turning them off. You can also look at the dependencies for your application and determine if you really need them or if they can be easily removed. In addition, you’ll want to look at the licenses for your dependencies and make sure you understand the limitations placed on them and how that might affect your ability to publish your software. Once you are ready to publish, you’ll want to take the time to test your system on multiple different platforms, operating systems, computer types, and just about anywhere you think a user might try to use it. You may also want to explore adding some easy configuration options to your application - both Java and Python include implementations of the dotenv library from the Ruby programming that make this really simple. You should also make sure your code doesn’t contain any sensitive information such as API keys or passwords - there are lots of horror stories online of companies being compromised due to sensitive information being pushed to a GitHub repository. Finally, once you’ve reached the end and you’re ready to publish, you’ll be faced with one of the two hardest problems in computer science - naming things! You’ll need to come up with a hopefully unique and catchy name for your application so others can find it easily.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 13:35:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/ii-gui/15-releases/02-preparing-for-release/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>