<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Type Systems :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/04-type-systems/video/index.html</link>
    <description>Resources Slides Video Script Before we dive deeper into object-oriented programming, let’s go through a brief refresher about data types and type systems. You most likely learned about this in your first programming course, but at that time it probably didn’t make much sense since you were new to everything. However, now that you have some programming experience, you’ll be able to better understand these concepts and reframe your knowledge a bit. First, recall that each programming language supports several data types known as “primitives.” These are built into the language itself, and represent the simplest forms of data the language knows how to properly represent. Shown here are the most commonly used primitive data type for Java and Python. For whole numbers, they both use an integer data type. For floating-point values, Java uses a type called double while Python uses a similar type called float. Both languages also support a data type for a simple Boolean value as well. Finally, both languages can store single characters and whole strings of characters, but these come with a few caveats. In Java, the character type is a primitive, but the String type is technically a class that stores multiple characters together. However, since Strings are so widely used in Java, they can be thought of as a primitive in some ways. Conversely, Python treats the string type as a built-in primitive, but doesn’t support a special type for a single character. Instead, a string with length 1 is a stand-in for the character type supported by most other languages.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:04:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/i-oop/02-object-oriented-programming/04-type-systems/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>