




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UML on CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in UML on CC 410 Textbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/01-introduction/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/01-introduction/index.html</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this chapter was adapted from Nathan Bean&amp;rsquo;s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author&amp;rsquo;s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.
As software systems became more complex, it became harder to talk and reason about them. Unified Modeling Language (UML) attempted to correct for this by providing a visual, diagrammatic approach to communicate the structure and function of a program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UML</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/02-uml/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/02-uml/index.html</guid>
      <description>Video Materials
1
Unified Modeling Language (UML) was introduced to create a standardized way of visualizing a software system design. It was developed by Grady Booch, Ivar Jacobson, and James Rumbah at Rational Software in the mid-nineties. It was adopted as a standard by the Object Management Group in 1997, and also by the International Organization for Standardization (ISO) as an approved ISO standard in 2005.
The UML standard actually provides many different kinds of diagrams for describing a software system - both structure and behavior:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxes</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/03-boxes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/03-boxes/index.html</guid>
      <description>UML class diagrams are largely composed of boxes - basically a rectangular border containing text. UML class diagrams use boxes to represent units of code - i.e. classes, structs, and enumerations. These boxes are broken into compartments. For example, an Enum is broken into two compartments:
Stereotypes UML is intended to be language-agnostic. But we often find ourselves in situations where we want to convey language-specific ideas, and the UML specification leaves room for this with stereotypes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typed Elements</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/04-typed-elements/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/04-typed-elements/index.html</guid>
      <description>A second basic building block for UML diagrams is a typed element. Typed elements (as you might expect from the name) have a type. Fields and parameters are typed elements, as are method parameters and return values.
The pattern for defining a typed element is:
[visibility] element: type [constraint]The optional [visibility] indicates the visibility of the element, the element is the name of the typed element, and the type is its type, and the [constraint] is an optional constraint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classes</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/05-classes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/05-classes/index.html</guid>
      <description>Video Materials
In a UML class diagram, individual classes are represented with a box divided into three compartments, each of which is for displaying specific information:
The first compartment identifies the class - it contains the name of the class. The second compartment holds the attributes of the class (the fields and properties). And the third compartment holds the operations of the class (the methods) of the class.
In the diagram above, we can see the Fruit class modeled on the right side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Associations</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/06-associations/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/06-associations/index.html</guid>
      <description>Video Materials
Class diagrams also express the associations between classes by drawing lines between the boxes representing them.
There are two basic types of associations we model with UML: has-a and is-a associations. We break these into two further categories, based on the strength of the association, which is either strong or weak. These associations are:
Association NameAssociation TypeTypical UsageRealizationweak is-aInterfacesGeneralizationstrong is-aInheritanceAggregationweak has-aCollectionsCompositionstrong has-aEncapsulationIs-A Associations Is-a associations indicate a relationship where one class is a instance of another class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating UML Diagrams</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/07-creating-diagrams/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/07-creating-diagrams/index.html</guid>
      <description>There are many tools available to help you develop your own UML diagrams. Here are a few that we recommend using for this course.
Diagrams.net Most of the graphics used in the Computational Core program, including the UML diagrams in this and previous courses, are made using the free Diagrams.net tool.
When creating a new diagram, you can select the UML Diagram template to get started. The interface is really simple and easy to use, with lots of drag-and-drop components you can add to your diagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UML Example</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/08-uml-example/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/08-uml-example/index.html</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s work through an example of creating a UML class diagram based on existing code. This is loosely based off a project from an earlier course, so some of the structure may be familiar.
The Project This project is a number calculator that makes use of object-oriented concepts such as inheritance, interfaces, and polymorphism to represent different types of numbers using different classes. We&amp;rsquo;ll also follow the Model-View-Controller (MVC) architectural pattern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/09-summary/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ksu-cs-textbooks.github.io/cc410/i-oop/05-uml/09-summary/index.html</guid>
      <description>In this section, we learned about UML class diagrams, a language-agnostic approach to visualizing the structure of an object-oriented software system. We saw how individual classes are represented by boxes divided into three compartments; the first for the identity of the class, the second for its attributes, and the third for its operators. We learned that italics are used to indicate abstract classes and operators, and underlining static classes, attributes, and operators.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>