<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Extras :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/index.html</link>
    <description>Extra Content!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:13:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installing Git on Windows</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/01-installing-git/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/01-installing-git/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Git Installers Install Git from GitHub Git Guides GitHub Desktop Adding a new SSH Key to your GitHub Account from GitHub Video Script Hello and welcome to the first of a series of videos where I’m going to show you everything you need to know to be able to bring your CC 410 projects and other Computational Core projects outside of Codio and onto your local system. For these videos, I’m doing this all on Windows, which is the most complicated system to set up. For Mac and Linux users, there are similar things that you can do on those systems. If you want me to cover those in a future video, just let me know, and I’d be happy to do that, or you can find really good documentation online. In this video, we’re going to go through installing the Git tool on Windows and also how we can connect it to GitHub and download our projects using Git. So let’s get started with that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Python</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/02-installing-python/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/02-installing-python/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Python Installers Virtual Environments and Packages Python venv Package Video Script In this video, we’re going to go through the process of installing Python on Windows and configuring it to work with our CC 410 projects. To begin, I’ve downloaded the latest Python installer from the Python website, and I’m going to run that installer to install Python on Windows. In the Python installer, there are a couple of options that are not checked by default that we absolutely want to make sure we check. First, I’m going to check mark the option at the bottom that says Add Python 3.10 to PATH, which allows me to use Python in tools such as PowerShell, as well as additional IDEs. I’m also going to click the Customize Installation option to change a few of the other options. The first page I’m going to leave everything is the default. And then on the second page, I’m going to check mark the option that says install for all users. That will place Python in the C:\Program Files\Python folder instead of buried somewhere else. With that, I’ll click install and it will install Python. Once Python is installed, we’ll click Close to close the installer. We don’t need to disable the path length limit for most of our projects, but this is something you could do if you find you run into trouble later on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Java</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/03-installing-java/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/03-installing-java/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Java JDK Installers Gradle Downloads Video Script In this video, I’m going to go over installing Java and Gradle on Windows. So I’ve already downloaded the Java Development Kit directly from the Oracle website. So I’m going to briefly double click to install that.&#xA;I’ll also install Gradle. However, Gradle does not come with an installer, it just has a ZIP file. So to install Gradle, we’re going to extract this ZIP file, and we’re going to extract it to the folder C:\Gradle. Once I’ve extracted the Gradle files, I’ll open up the Gradle folder, and then the bin folder. And I’m going to click up here in the address bar and copy that path. We need to add this path to our Windows path so that we can actually access these files in the search bar. If I start typing environments, it should give me an option to edit my system environment variables. So I’ll choose that option, then click environment variables. And then under system variables, I’ll find the path variable and choose Edit. And then I’m going to create a new entry and paste in that path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python IDEs</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/04-python-ides/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/04-python-ides/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Download PyCharm Download Visual Studio Code Python in Visual Studio Code Video Script Now let’s look at a couple of common IDEs for Python and see how we can use those with the projects that we’ve already configured. For this example, I’m going to install both PyCharm and Visual Studio Code. So to do that, I’m going to begin by installing both of those IDEs. When you’re installing PyCharm, it does present you with a quite a few options that you can choose from. Depending on your particular setup, you may wish to check mark things such as updating your PATH variable, updating your Windows context menu, and associating the .py file extension with this tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java IDEs</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/05-java-ides/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iv-extras/05-java-ides/index.html</guid>
      <description>Resources Download IntelliJ Download Visual Studio Code Java in Visual Studio Code Java Build Tools in VS Code Video Script In this video, I’m going to discuss how to install and configure two popular IDEs for Java to work with our projects. Those IDEs are IntelliJ and VS Code. First, let’s look at installing those two IDEs. I’ve already downloaded the installers, and so now I’m going to install both the IntelliJ IDE, and Visual Studio code. When installing IntelliJ, it gives you many different options that you may want to enable depending on how you’re using the tool. I’m going to enable adding it to the PATH, adding open folders project and associating the .java file extension.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>