




  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>REST and Forms :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/</link>
    <description>HTML Form Data and Sensible URL Schemes!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:13:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/01-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/01-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this page was adapted from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author’s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.&#xA;Now that we have explored some ideas about getting data from the web server, let’s turn our attention to sending data to the web server. One of the earliest approaches for doing so is to use a HTML form sent as a HTTP Request, which we’ll take a look at in this chapter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML Forms</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/02-html-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/02-html-forms/</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this page was adapted from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author’s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.&#xA;Video Materials&#xA;One of the earliest (and still widely used) mechanisms for transferring data from a browser (client) to the server is a form. The &lt;form&gt; is a specific HTML element that contains input fields and buttons the user can interact with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form Data</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/03-form-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/03-form-data/</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this page was adapted from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author’s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.&#xA;Form data is simply serialized key/value pairs pulled from a form and encoded using one of the three possible encoding strategies. Let’s look at each in turn.&#xA;x-www-form-urlencoded The default encoding method is application/x-www-form-urlencoded, which encodes the form data as a string consisting of key/value pairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring and Form Data</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/04-spring-form-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/04-spring-form-data/</guid>
      <description>Once we’ve built a website that can send form data using an HTTP POST request to our web application, we need some way to access that information in our controller. Let’s look at how we would accomplish this in Spring.&#xA;Spring Path Variables In a previous example, we saw how we can create a route that includes variables directly in the path itself:&#xA;@GetMapping(&#34;/greeting/{name}&#34;) public String greetingWithName(@PathVariable String name, Model model) { model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flask and Form Data</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/05-flask-form-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/05-flask-form-data/</guid>
      <description>Once we’ve built a website that can send form data using an HTTP POST request to our web application, we need some way to access that information in our controller. Let’s look at how we would accomplish this in Flask.&#xA;Flask Path Variables In a previous example, we saw how we can create a route that includes variables directly in the path itself:&#xA;@route(&#39;/greeting/&lt;name&gt;/&#39;) def greeting_with_name(self, name): &#34;&#34;&#34;Display greeting with name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESTful Routes</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/06-restful-routes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/06-restful-routes/</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this page was adapted from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author’s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.&#xA;Video Materials&#xA;Many web applications deal with some kind of resource, i.e. people, widgets, records. Much like in object-orientation we have organized the program around objects, many web applications are organized around resources. And as we have specialized ways to construct, access, and destroy objects, web applications need to create, read, update, and destroy resource records (we call these CRUD operations).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validation</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/07-validation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/07-validation/</guid>
      <description>Content Note Much of the content in this page was adapted from Nathan Bean’s CIS 400 course at K-State, with the author’s permission. That content is licensed under a Creative Commons BY-NC-SA license.&#xA;Validation refers to the process of making sure the submitted data matches our expectations. Validation can be done client-side or server-side. For example, we can use the built-in HTML form validation properties to enforce rules, like a number that must be positive:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/08-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/iii-web/17-rest-forms/08-summary/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter we looked at how data is handled in web applications. We saw how forms can be used to submit data to our server, and examined several common encoding strategies. We also saw how we can retrieve this data in our web application by examining the routes or the form data submitted. We also explored the concept of RESTful routes. Finally, we discussed validating submitted values, on both the client and server side of a HTTP request.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>