




  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
	  

  
	
		
		
	  

  
	
	  

  
	
		
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spring 2021 :: CC 410 Textbook</title>
    <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week01/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to CC 410. My name is Russell Feldhausen. I’m going to be your instructor for this semester. And this is the first of the weekly announcements videos that I’m going to do in this class. My goal is throughout the semester, if I have anything interesting to talk about each week, I will try and record a video and post it sometime around Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 2</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week02/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week two announcements video for CC 410 in Spring 2021. So this week, you should be wrapping up module one and hello real world, the first example projects in this class, they were actually both due Sunday night. But if you haven’t gotten them completed, you can still turn them in right now, check the late policy in the syllabus for the exact details of the late policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 3</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week03/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Good morning, and welcome to the week three announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021, this has been a busy second week of the class. But hopefully at this point you should be, you should have already met with me for your final project milestone one where we discuss some ideas for your final project. I believe I’ve covered almost everybody in this class at this point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 4</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week04/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 4 announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021. So you should be wrapping up at this point all of the stuff for module three, which is the documentation, testing and UML module. It’s one of the larger modules in terms of tutorial content. And also in terms of the actual final project, or the restaurant project content, writing unit tests is a lot of code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 5</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week05/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week five announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021. So this week we’re wrapping up the second week working on modules four, and five. So hopefully by now you’ve turned in the stuff on inheritance and polymorphism along with the example that gives you a good idea of what you’re doing in milestone three. There’s also some other things you can do right now, the start-stop-continue survey, which is really good chance to give me feedback, if there’s anything you’d like me to start doing in this class or make sure I continue doing or if there’s anything that I’m doing that you’d prefer that I stopped doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 6</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week06/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week six enhancements video for CC 410 in Spring 2021. We’re over a third of the way through the semester at this point. So hopefully should be wrapping up the stuff from last week, which was on debugging and logging and lambda expressions. There was also a restaurant milestone, this is the last of the data part of the restaurant milestone before we move into the GUI part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 7</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week07/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021, for week seven. So some quick updates for this week I posted last week. But hopefully you all saw this I have moved all the course deadlines from Sundays to Mondays. Part of that is to give you a little bit more time to work on the projects. But also a lot of that is to give you the chance to work on the weekends, and then give me a chance to catch up with questions on Mondays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 8</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week08/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the CC 410 video for week eight in spring 2021. So this point you should be wrapping up restaurant milestone five, which is where you add a lot of event based programming into your GUIs. And so hopefully it’s been going well, I realize I’m a little bit behind on grading, but I will be getting caught up this week, as we’ll talk about here in just a second because I have something to do this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 9</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week09/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week nine announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021. So this week, I’m a little bit behind getting stuff post to the Canvas, but it will be posted shortly. I’m waiting on the last couple of videos to get rendered from our videographers. But this week, we’ll be starting on working with external libraries. And so we’ll learn about those external libraries we’ve been installing in our programs, how to use them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 10</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week10/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello and welcome to the CC 410 week 10 video for spring 2021. You’re working on a double week this week so this week is basically continuing the stuff that you’ve been doing for week nine and week 10. So this week you’re going to focus on releases where we actually take our software and package it into a release package that you could then share online you could upload to some of the package managers that we’ve seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 11</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week11/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 11 announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021. We’re on week 11, which is starting the next set of restaurant milestones. And so this week, we’re transferring our focus from actual desktop GUIs to data driven websites. So this chapter, we’re going to introduce the World Wide Web, we’re going to talk about all sorts of different web technologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 12</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week12/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the CC 410 announcements video for week 12 in spring 2021, so we’ve made it to week 12. And this week we’re working on HTML forms and the REST architecture. Most of them are going to focus on HTML forms in the example and in the project. But we’re going to talk a little bit about REST and some other things that will set the stage for what we’re going to do in the next milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 13</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week13/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 13 announcements video for CC 410 in Spring 2021. So we’re at almost at the end of the semester and this week, we’re going to be covering restful architecture and how to build a RESTful API in our web applications. This week, the textbook chapter on web API’s is not quite finished as of Monday when I record this, so I’ll be posting that probably later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 14</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week14/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 14 announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021. Well, we’re on week 14, we’re almost at the end of the semester. And so this week is really the last week of new content that we will be working with. So this week, we’re going to cover serialization in the textbook, which is the process of saving your program state to a file and then restoring that state from the file later on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring &#39;21 Week 15</title>
      <link>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textbooks.cs.ksu.edu/cc410/x-weekly-updates/old/spring-2021/week15/</guid>
      <description>Resources Slides Edited Transcript Hello, and welcome to the week 15 announcements video for CC 410 in spring 2021. We are on week 15, which means it’s dead week, there’s just this week and next week left in the semester. So there’s really not a whole lot left to this class. If you’ve been keeping up and you just turned in the last milestone and the last big chapter in the textbook, you’re pretty much almost done.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>